[
  {
    "question": "Which wireless technology has only limited reliability according to the speed of the\nmovement of the mobile equipment:",
    "answers": [3],
    "options": ["GSM", "GPRS", "UMTS", "Bluetooth", "WiFi"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which wireless technology offers the highest transmission rates:",
    "answers": [4],
    "options": ["GSM", "GPRS", "UMTS", "Bluetooth", "WiFi"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What type of the attack is the attack guided by the following motivation: \"The attacker wants to steal information, damage your system because of a grievance, or alter your system to acquire a tangible reward\":",
    "answers": [0],
    "options": ["Profit or revenge", "Profit", "Revenge", "Gaming", "Ego"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which one of the following attacks is NOT classified as a wireless attack:",
    "answers": [1],
    "options": [
      "Snooping",
      "Meet in the middle",
      "Modification",
      "Masquerading",
      "Denial of Service"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is \"one-time password\"?",
    "answers": [1],
    "options": [
      "You use one unique password for all your logons and connections.",
      "Each and every time you logon or connect, you use a new password.",
      "You use passwords with a time stamp in them.",
      "A password that you use for generating the master key.",
      "A password that you use for generating the session key."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "In the wireless communication terminology what the abbreviation MAC stands for?",
    "answers": [1],
    "options": [
      "Message Authentication Code",
      "Media Access Control",
      "Mobile Authentication Code",
      "Medium Accessibility Coding",
      "Military Air Command"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "According to the IEEE 802 standard, what is the right ordering of the layers:",
    "answers": [1],
    "options": [
      "MAC Layer, IP Layer, TCP Layer, LLC Layer, Application Layer",
      "MAC Layer, LLC Layer, IP Layer, TCP Layer, Application Layer",
      "LLC Layer, MAC Layer, IP Layer, TCP Layer, Application Layer",
      "LLC Layer, MAC Layer, TCP Layer, IP Layer, Application Layer",
      "MAC Layer, LLC Layer, TCP Layer, IP Layer, Application Layer"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "If a station moves only within BSS, then this type of mobility is known as:",
    "answers": [0],
    "options": [
      "No transition mobility",
      "BSS transition",
      "Limited BSS transition",
      "ESS transition",
      "Limited ESS transition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "If station or AP sends a notice for association termination, then that service is known as:",
    "answers": [2],
    "options": [
      "Association",
      "Reassociation",
      "Disassociation",
      "Deassociation",
      "Quitassociation"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "The original 802.11 standard operated on the following frequencies:",
    "answers": [0],
    "options": [
      "2.4 GHz",
      "2.4 - 5.0 GHz",
      "900 MHz",
      "1.2 GHz",
      "900 MHz â€“ 1.3 GHz"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "The maximal data rate per channel in the original 802.11 standard was:",
    "answers": [4],
    "options": ["54 Mbps", "16 Mbps", "11 Mbps", "4 Mbps", "2 Mbps"]
  },
  {
    "question": "How many IVs are available in WEP?",
    "answers": [0],
    "options": [
      "<math><msup><mn>2</mn><mn>4</mn></msup></math>",
      "<math><msup><mn>2</mn><mn>64</mn></msup></math>",
      "<math><msup><mn>2</mn><mn>128</mn></msup></math>",
      "<math><mn>0</mn></math>",
      "<math><mn>24</mn></math>"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is true for WEP?",
    "answers": [4],
    "options": [
      "Mobile station and the access point get a session key from the LAN",
      "Mobile station have a master key and produces a session key for the access point",
      "Mobile station sends a key to the access point",
      "Mobile station have a different key than the access point",
      "Mobile station shares key with access point"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "In Wi-Fi what is the \"gold standard\"?",
    "answers": [4],
    "options": [
      "That was the first certification standard that came from Motorola.",
      "That was the second security standard that came from an alliance of hardware producers.",
      "The pin connection in the mobile equipment has to be made by gold.",
      "The pin connection in the mobile equipment has to be made by gold or silver.",
      "To obtain the Wi-Fi certification - the product has to be compatible with the set of \"gold standard\" products."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What encryption algorithm is used in WPA?",
    "answers": [3],
    "options": [
      "RC4 with 40 bits key",
      "RC4 with 104 bits key",
      "AES with 128 bits key",
      "RC4 with 128 bits key",
      "AES with 256 bits key"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the length of the user's secret key in GSM technology?",
    "answers": [4],
    "options": [
      "There is no such a security in GSM",
      "56 bits",
      "64 bits",
      "96 bits",
      "128 bits"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "In GSM, when a mobile is switched on, it registers its current location in a",
    "answers": [3],
    "options": [
      "Authentication Centre",
      "Roaming Data Center",
      "Visitor Location Register",
      "Home Location Register",
      "Nearest Base Station"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "\"Protect against someone tracking the location of the user or identifying calls made to or from the user by eavesdropping on the radio path\" is the following GSM security feature:",
    "answers": [4],
    "options": [
      "Encryption",
      "Handover",
      "Authentication",
      "Confidentiality",
      "Anonymity"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "In UMTS what kind of protection provides the \"Protection mode 2\" of MPSec?",
    "answers": [0],
    "options": [
      "Both integrity protection and encryption.",
      "Just integrity protection.",
      "Just encryption.",
      "Just message authentication.",
      "No protection"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the crucial protocol in IMS?",
    "answers": [2],
    "options": [
      "DH key-exchange",
      "AuC protocol",
      "Session Initiation Protocol",
      "The Proxy CSCF",
      "The Interrogating CSCF"
    ]
  }
]
